[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 37]
Senior.
Come on.
Sit here.
Senior.
I was looking through my mother's luggage the other day
and saw these.
I thought
these must be prepared for my wedding,
so I brought them here for you to take a look .
Rong.
These are not for current use.
Look.
This hairpin
was carved from a phoenix tree
that I found through hard work.
I set up a formation
to gather the essence of heaven and earth for seventy-seven forty-nine days
before using it as the raw material for carving.
Is it glossy?
You wasted so much time and cultivation
just for such a hairpin?
Don't you think it's worth it?
What did you carve this odd-shaped hairpin
for?
Even if you can't become an Immortal,
you should keep improving yourself.
Do you understand my intention or not?
Senior.
I knew
that perhaps the best bride-price for you
was for me to become an Immortal.
But I was useless
and failed to do it.
I'm sorry.
That's why I made this hairpin with my own hands
as my courtship token to you.
I like it.
I have to find a way to clear the evil spirit of the immortal root
for her.
My Lord!
Mr. Tai.
Has Fu already usurped the position of Demon King?
He ended up continuing
his wrongdoing.
My Lord.
You could only rely on water energy
to relieve your serious injuries.
While General Fu plotted against you
and took away your water energy.
He did it to kill you.
His mind has been bewitched by others.
He is no longer that Fu I once knew.
What he wants is...
the entire Three Realms.
All he wants
is for Luo Ning to come back.
He is chasing
an unachievable dream.
Mr. Tai.
Please do me a favor.
At your service.
Fu's purpose is Four Seasons Monument.
Tell Luo Ge and Liu Shao
to be careful of Fu.
I'll go find them now.
General Fu!
Since you are so loyal to my brother,
you should stay in Demon Palace forever
to take care of him.
Mr. Tai.
Mr. Tai!
Brother.
I'll attack  Immortal Palace myself
to show them
that it's useless to be careful.
I can do
whatever I want to do.
I can definitely bring Luo Ning back.
You can scold me if you want to.
Don't look at me like that.
No one can stop me from saving Luo Ning.
I know
you want to split Four Seasons Monument.
You still need Moon Sword anyhow.
Then we'll get his Moon Sword.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You don't need to worry about anything
with such strong cultivation.
You don't have to take part in the attack on the Demon Palace.
Why?
I'm afraid you would hesitate.
Are you worried that I would help Luo Ge?
But didn't you also say
that you didn't want Luo Ge to die?
I did want to spare him from death.
But that would only be possible
if Luo Ge was willing to split the Four Seasons Monument for Luo Ning.
All those who prevent me from rescuing Luo Ning
deserve to die.
He is so untrustworthy.
Fu.
In that case,
I'm going to spoil your plan too.
I will make you regret it.
I heard that the new Demon King
has set up heavy guards.
Who would dare to break in?
However, Demon King and the leaders are not here,
and all the masters have returned to land,
so we should be careful.
Mr. Tai.
Has something happened to the demon world?
Why did fu become Demon King?
What about He Na?
Mr. Tai, say something.
Mr. Tai!
You finally came.
Immortal Master?
Who is it?
The traitor I saw that day
was you?
No.
Immortal Master has always been upright.
He wouldn't do this.
You are not Immortal Master.
Can't you recognize me?
Is everything ready?
Everything is prepared,
except for one thing.
Then let Luo Ge
send that thing here in person.
Rong.
Senior.
What book are you reading?
I'm looking for
a way to clear the evil spirit of the immortal root.
I've looked for it.
There is no other way
except to enable Xilun Formation.
But to enable this useless Xilun Formation,
either I need to get Sun Spring and sacrifice a disciple's life,
or
I have to sacrifice the best Immortal
as the eye of formation.
I can't sacrifice other people's lives
just because I want to be Immortal.
If that's the only way,
I'd rather not become an Immortal.
Rong.
Four Seasons Monument...
Luo Ge.
What's going on?
Someone disturbed the sealed spiritual source
and seriously injured Xie Lingqi.
Immortal Luo Ge.
Masters.
The new King of the demon world and their masters
are attacking us from the back mountain.
It's Fu.
Immortal Master is already there.
He asked me to get you
and two masters to help.
Now?
Yes.
You guys
go help Immortal Master.
I will try my best
to hold up Four Seasons Monument.
Fu's cultivation is not top-notch.
We'll deal with the Demons.
Just concentrate on restoring Four Seasons Monument.
Okay.
I knew
it was you behind all this again.
Then guess
who will win
this time.
How dare you
try to invade Immortal Palace?
He Na!
It's useless.
You are unable to open the boundary alone.
Ridiculous.
You better give up.
Bai Feng?
Why are you here?
What are you planning again?
I'm not here to deal with you this time.
Fu
has been planning on something evil.
He's even trying to hurt Luo Ge now.
He's no match for Luo Ge.
You'll have to listen to me
if you want to break this boundary.
Fu conspired against Demon King
and took away his water energy.
He is invincible
in the Three Realms now.
I am now going to break this boundary as well.
I'm going to
let go of the people
Fu wants to trap.
The reason why he forbade me to go to Immortal Palace
must be because he tried to kill Luo Ge.
As for our grudge,
I will settle it with you sooner or later.
I will also
settle every evil deed
you have done with you.
He Na!
He Na.
Wake up, He Na!
How is it?
Fu
even hurt his own brother.
He's simply insane.
He plotted against Demon King
to take part of his water energy,
and made a deal with the demon under the Four Seasons Monument
to borrow part of the power of Supreme God.
What exactly is he trying to do?
Bewitched by that demon,
he believed that Luo Ning's immortal energy
had been exiled under Four Seasons Monument.
So,
now he wants to get the Moon Sword
to break Four Seasons Monument
and find Luo Ning's immortal energy.
When I sneaked in here,
I found that the guards here were very loose.
There are no masters at all.
He has already led these masters
to attack Four Seasons Monument.
I thought
that he would not hurt Luo Ge
for Luo Ning's sake.
But I found that even Demon King in White was hurt by him,
so I stopped counting on him.
Fu is really insane.
Luo Ge!
Luo Ge, can you hear me?
Answer me if you are safe.
Could Luo Ge have already been plotted against?
Immortal Palace has boundaries.
Fu can't get in.
He Na.
Liu Shao.
Hurry back and inform Luo Ge
that the boundaries in Immortal Palace
can no longer stop Fu.
Using Melody Flute
can help you suppress him.
I'm going to inform Luo Ge right now.
Take care of yourself.
I'll go with you.
I can help.
Luo Ge.
Now that you are injured,
you can't beat me.
As long as I hold out until the Demons are defeated,
you lose.
Do you really think so?
As long as Fu gets Moon Sword,
then you lose.
Who is it?
Luo Ge.
I don't want to make Luo Ning sad,
so I won't kill you.
But you have already lost most of your spiritual power,
and couldn't beat me now.
Be smart,
and hand over your Moon Sword.
So,
your so-called attacking Immortal Palace
is just a lie.
And your real purpose
is Four Seasons Monument.
Everyone,
Demon King has succeeded.
He asked us to go back to the demon world first.
Bai Feng?
Didn't Demon King forbid you to come to Immortal Palace?
He made me stay in the demon world
just to keep me on call.
What?
I've worked for him for so long.
Don't you believe me?
Come with me!
Retreat!
Senior.
What's going on?
I don't know.
We can't let them go.
Wait.
Don't you think it's weird?
Fu is not here.
Should we go back to Lusitai first?
But there must be something wrong
about this sudden move of the Demons.
Where's Luo Ge?
Luo Ge is guarding the Four Seasons Monument at Lusitai.
Just him?
Besides him,
there seems to be Immortal Master there.
But Bai Feng said
that Immortal Master Wanwu has been bewitched by that demon.
What?
We've been tricked.
Four Seasons Monument is not the point.
The point is that Luo Ning's immortal energy is under Four Seasons Monument.
And the person under that monument
can help me see Luo Ning again.
Don't mention Luo Ning.
A man like you
who would even hurt his own brother
is not worthy of my sister.
What happened between me and my brother has nothing to do with you.
I just borrowed his strength temporarily.
I will use the Three Realms to pay him back.
Temporarily?
He Na was seriously injured because of you in the Great Wilderness,
and he could only rely on the power of water energy to relieve his injuries.
Taking his water energy now
is no different from taking his life.
Stop scaremongering.
No one
can prevent me from seeing Luo Ning again.
Ge.
I'll deal with him.
Immortal Master,
he now has 30% of the power of Supreme God.
And he also combined it with He Na's water energy.
You're no match for him.
I'll do it.
Luo Ge,
be careful with Immortal Master Wanwu.
It turns out...
that you are no longer Immortal Master.
It's too late.
Luo Ge.
Hand over the Moon Sword,
and I will return it to you
after I rescue Luo Ning.
Let's see if you can get it.
I'll fulfill you.
I can do anything
to save Luo Ning.
You should be the one to bear this demonic poison.
Do you now know how much pain
Luo Ning has endured for you?
Do you still want her to stay here alone?
No.
I will return it to you later.
Luo Ning.
Come out!
Luo Ning's divine spirit
is just below the God of the Moonlight's half heart.
You have split the Four Seasons Monument.
Let me help you
release Supreme God.
Luo Ning.
Liu Shao?
Liu Shao.
Stop making useless attempts.
Even Luo Ge couldn't stop me,
let alone you.
Luo Ge!
Luo Ge, wake up!
Melody Flute?
You're late.
Supreme God has been released by me already.
He will be out soon.
My Luo Ning
will also be revived.
It has been ten thousand years.
The day has finally arrived.
Rong.
Let's enable Xilun Formation
before he comes out.
No...
Let's get rid of the evil spirit
and return that half heart to Luo Ge
to help him become God.
Doing so can not only save Luo Ge,
but also preserve the Three Realms.
Go and help Luo Ge over.
What are you waiting for?
Luo Ge will become a demon
if we wait any longer.
But no one
can be the eye of formation.
I can.
I can't let you take that risk.
No.
You should be decisive
as a man.
If we fail this time,
you will be responsible for protecting Immortal Palace.
Senior.
Do you really think this simple Xilun Formation
can stop me?
I'm about to make it.
Don't ruin my plan!
Xilun Formation.
No!
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning hasn't come out yet.
Come on!
Luo Ge!
You suppressed the evil spirit
and became Supreme God.
But the evil spirit has not been completely eliminated.
Rong.
You've finally become an Immortal.
Senior!
Master Zhuo!
Senior.
You will be fine.
Hang in there.
Senior.
I have become Immortal.
Did you see this?
Senior!
You said you would marry me
as soon as I became Immortal.
Senior.
Senior!
Luo Ge.
Please help me
save her.
I can't help you.
You are now Supreme God.
You must be able to save her, right?
I'm sorry.
You will come back, right?
I'll wait for you
to come back and marry me.
These are the six talisman pearls I used to maintain the Four Seasons Monument.
You will become an Immortal.
Your talisman pearls were tempered
during the suppression of Four Seasons Monument,
which could greatly improve your cultivation.
This can be regarded as your reward from the Four Seasons Monument.
Why?
Why didn't Luo Ning come out?
Could it be...
Could it be that you guys hid her?
She must be in that half of your heart.
Luo Ning is not under Four Seasons Monument.
Outside Four Seasons Monument,
there are countless wronged souls caused by you.
It was you who caused my sister to die with regret.
Is there...
Is there really no way
to bring Luo Ning back?
My sister was protecting you before she died,
so I tried to spare you.
But you were so obsessed that you have caused chaos in the Three Realms
and caused people to suffer.
Today I will kill you, the chief culprit,
for the sake of the Three Realms.
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning!
This is Luo Ning's immortal energy.
Moon Sword didn't hurt him
because he was protected by Bone-corroding Harp's spiritual power.
This saved Luo Ning's sense.
♫In the sea of clouds, I looked at the reflection of the moon in the water♫
Fu.
You did something bad again.
Luo Ning.
♫I kept waiting and arched my palms into a circle♫
I've been looking for you.
And all this time you have always been in...
the Wishful Bead.
♫The reflection gradually reminded me of our first meeting♫
♫I can no longer tell the difference between wind and rain♫
Luo Ning.
♫Even if I get the volley sword♫
We have been looking for Luo Ning's immortal energy.
♫I can't forget you♫
It turned out
♫Our destiny has been sealed long ago♫
she had been with Fu all along.
She has been by Fu's side
♫I have no other choice♫
with the last bit of spiritual power of Bone-corroding Harp.
Luo Ning!
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
♫For billions of years♫
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
In this war,
Four Seasons Monument was destroyed,
♫A few hasty nights♫
Immortal Master was bewitched by the evil spirit and fell into a coma,
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
and Master Zhuo
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
was petrified by the Xilun Formation.
We have lost so much
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch, and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
just to purify this half of my heart.
It turns out that Luo Ning
has been by Fu's side all along.
♫The remaining flowers in the mirror reflect the moon in the water♫
♫We can't live up to such a good time♫
I heard
that he not only killed Fairy Luo Ning,
but also took his brother's water energy.
♫Recalling the unforgettable glance at the beginning♫
A villain like him
will definitely be devoured by the evil spirit immediately
after entering there.
He deserves it.
♫I realized that it was a thousand years ago♫
Go.
♫Is this bad luck, or good luck?♫
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
♫The past has passed, so do not linger♫
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch, and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
♫Life is like a grain of sand♫
♫It burns the fire in my heart♫
Luo Ning.
♫I want to burn myself to hear you say that you have never changed♫
I've done so many wrong things.
Are you still protecting me?
Is it worth it?
I will deal with you.
Don't you hurt Luo Ning!
Come on!
I heard
that General Fu
was imprisoned in Bone Melting Pool.
With the chaos he caused,
it's reasonable for him
to end his life in Bone Melting Pool.
But he is my only brother after all.
I was also responsible
for the way things have turned out.
After all,
I pampered him too much,
to make him such a villain.
My Lord,
you two brothers are the only ones left with the blood of Demon King.
I don't know how long General Fu
can survive in Bone Melting Pool.
And your injury is so serious.
Aren't you worried
the Demons will lose their king in the future?
But the things he did this time
has brought disaster to the Three Realms.
I can't help him.
I just hope
he can truly repent
and stop doing wrong things.
Although Master Zhuo was petrified,
she may still survive.
Why didn't Supreme God Luo Ge
try to save her?
Girl.
What did you say?
I mean,
with Master Zhuo's situation,
it is possible
for Supreme God to save her.
I'm just worried
if it's because the evil spirit on that half of the heart
hasn't been removed,
so he couldn't use the power of Supreme God
as he wants.
If so,
what if
he accidentally loses his mind
like God of the Moonlight?
Luo Ge.
You didn't expect
that I would come out in the end, did you?
And
I came into this world through your body.
Do you think
you'll win?
Get lost!
What's the matter with the weather?
Would Immortal Palace have rainstorms and thunderstorms like the human world?
The lightning and thunder
reminded me of the birth
of that evil spirit ten thousand years ago.
Ten thousand years ago?
That's right.
I had just transformed into a human being at that time.
The weather was the same then as it is now.
Later I found out
that it was because that evil spirit came out.
Could it be that Luo Ge has been...
Luo Ge?
Luo Ge!